I know you are that reporter's daughter.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Reporter Gu's death back then
was caused by our family.
Please give me a chance to make it up to you.
How do you know my identity?
Mucheng.
She told me everything.
What do you want to do?
I want to cooperate with you.
Send my father to prison.
This...
You heard me right.
I will choose justice over family,
no matter the cost.
Why?
Because he never
treated me like his own son.
Back then,
he drove my mother away for his own selfish desires.
Since then,
he has ignored me,
putting all his effort...
were all poured into
my half-brother.
Be careful not to fall.
Finally, I founded Shengli Media.
Congratulations, Mr. Ling.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Mr. Lin.
Just as the company was improving,
it was forcibly taken by him again.
What are you doing?
Who let you in?
It became one of his tools to consolidate upper-level relationships.
Mucheng
is one of the victims.
I have always longed for the day
when I can personally seek justice for myself and my mother.
Lawyer Gu.
In the phone
is some video evidence
recorded by your father before he passed away.
And in this hard drive
is some evidence of the company's financial irregularities.
But this evidence alone
is not enough to go against my father.
We still need more compelling evidence.
Lawyer Gu,
the only person who can defeat my father now
is you.
So I want to ask for your help.
You believed that guy?
I can't figure it out.
I really can't figure it out.
You said based on previous experiences,
Lingze must really hate his dad.
But I didn't think he hated him enough
to betray him.
He actually handed such important evidence
directly to me.
This is enough to convict him.
It's really hard to figure out.
Could it be that in the previous timelines,
we complicated things?
Forget it. Let's not think about it.
So much has happened today.
Let's get some rest first.
You should go to bed early too.
Leave these with me.
He called us over so early in the morning.
What does he want to do now?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Mr. Ling, you called us over in such a hurry.
Is there something wrong?
I have something to give you.
My father has made a new move.
He is preparing to launch a group live broadcast plan this time.
This plan
was personally designed by my father.
I always feel something is wrong with this group broadcast.
So,
I want to hear your opinions.
On the surface,
this broadcast plan seems fine.
But given what your father did before
by using the streamers,
I have reason to suspect
that this new broadcast plan
must be hiding some unknown secrets.
Then what should I do?
To avoid your father's suspicion,
my suggestion is
that you proceed with the plan
and collect evidence at the same time.
Once you find out that those so-called higher-ups
really have ulterior motives against the streamers,
take action immediately.
Okay, I'll do as you say.
Good luck.
I will.
Hello, guys.
I'm Mucheng. Long time no see.
Did you miss me?
Those rumors on the internet are false.
I'm very happy with the company.
From now on,
I will meet you all with a new streaming style.
Welcome the new streamer.
Come on, everyone, say hello.
Those people replied.
Take a screenshot first.
Okay.
I'll send them all to you later.
Come on.
Keep up the good work.
Mr. Ling.
I really like the new live streaming model.
The girls you paired up are all excellent.
In the future,
I will lead them to achieve even better results.
Here's to you.
Mr. Ling.
Mr. Wang asked Mucheng to go over.
Tell him
today is an internal celebration party.
It's not convenient for me.
Mr. Ling.
Mr. Wang is here.
It wouldn't be good if we don't receive him, right?
I'm fine.
Sit down.
I told you to sit down.
Tell them it's not convenient today.
Yes.
You don't need to worry about this.
Why has she changed so much?
Could it be that I was wrong all along?
I just feel like
something is weird.
Mr. Ling,
you're not giving me any face.
Lao Wang,
you didn't even tell me you were coming.
What, am I not welcome?
Of course not.
As you can see,
this is our company's internal celebration party.
How about this? I'll find you later.
I just want to have a drink right now.
Okay, have a seat.
Chengcheng.
Play some music.
Mucheng,
it's only been a few days.
Why are you acting like a stranger again?
Mr. Wang,
how could I?
Come,
have a drink.
Mr. Wang, I'll drink with you.
Mr. Wang,
come,
let me introduce you
to our company's new team.
Each of you must toast Mr. Wang individually.
Did you hear me?
How can I handle all this?
Mr. Wang, a toast to you.
Okay.
Okay, bottoms up.
Everyone must finish their drink.
This little girl finished hers.
Come, let me pour you another.
Okay.
What's your name?
Hello, Mr. Wang. I'm Xiaoya.
Sit.
Come.
Keep Mr. Wang good company.
Come,
let's have another drink.
It's okay.
Trust me,
it will all be worth it.